doesfollow.com 2018-05-10

# DoesFollow - Find Out Who Follows Whom on Twitter - Privacy Policy

Kismet Ventures, LLC, a Texas limited liability company, d/b/a “doesfollow” (“ **doesfollow** ," “ **our** ,” “ **us** ,” or " **we** ") respects your privacy. In that regard, we have created this Privacy Policy to let you know what information we collect when you visit the website [www.doesfollow.com](https://www.doesfollow.com/) (the “ **Website** ”) and/or use our proprietary service (the “ **Service** ”), why we collect it, and how it is used.

###  Your Consent to this Privacy Policy

By using the Website or the Service, you agree to this Privacy Policy and the collection and use of information contemplated hereby. This is our entire and exclusive Privacy Policy and it supersedes any earlier version.

We may change this Privacy Policy by posting a new version of this Privacy Policy on our Website or through the Service, and it is your responsibility to review this policy periodically. When we do change the policy, we will also revise the "Revised" date and may notify you or post a message on the Website and/or through the Service. Your continued use of the Website or the Service constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any updates.

###  What information does doesfollow collect?

" **Personal Information** " means any information that may be used to identify an individual or your account, including, but not limited to, first and last name, screen names, home or other physical address, email address, phone number, age information, account tokens, and credit card or other payment information. We may ask you to provide Personal Information that will enable us to enhance your use of the Service, for purposes such as facilitating correspondence with you, registering your entitlement to access certain special features, or to complete transactions. It is always your choice whether or not to provide that Personal Information. If you choose not to provide requested Personal Information, you may not be able to use certain features of the Service.

**Technical Information.** We may collect and use technical data and related information—including but not limited to technical information about your device(s), system and application software, peripherals, location and use of the Service—that is gathered periodically to facilitate the provision of the Service, software updates, product support, and other services to you (if any) related to the Service. We may also automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser, which could include your IP address, cookie information, browser information, and the page you request. We do not deem any of this information to constitute Personal Information and while we will not use it in a way that associates such information with you (other than to deliver the Service to you), such information may be aggregated and used. doesfollow owns this information and may use it in any manner it deems appropriate.

###  How does doesfollow use Personal Information?

The Personal Information that you provide will be kept confidential and used to support your relationship with doesfollow and our products and services. Among other things, we want to help you quickly find information through our Service, leverage our tools in connection with your authorized use of our products and services, process payment, facilitate interaction with third party services that you opt into via the Service, and alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information and other new products and services from doesfollow.

###  Sharing of Personal Information

Except as set forth herein or in any applicable Terms of Service, doesfollow does not rent, sell or share Personal Information it collects about you to or with third parties, and Personal Information collected from you is only used to provide you with our products and services and to comply with any requirements of law.

Agents or contractors of doesfollow may have access to your Personal Information on a need-to-know basis for the purpose of performing services on behalf of doesfollow. All such agents or contractors who have access to such information are required to keep the information confidential and not use it for any other purpose than to carry out the services they are performing for doesfollow or as otherwise required by law.

We may also share certain Personal Information with certain doesfollow vendors in order to allow them to use that information to obtain and provide us with additional information about you. Any such vendors are required to keep the information we provide to them confidential and not use it for any other purpose than to carry out the services they are performing for doesfollow or as otherwise required by law. We believe that the information such vendors procure and provide to us help us support your relationship with doesfollow and our products and services.

doesfollow or its agents or contractors may disclose Personal Information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (1) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process; (2) protect and defend the rights or property of doesfollow or its agents or contractors; or (3) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public.

Finally, if doesfollow should ever merge with another organization, file for bankruptcy, or sell our assets, we may transfer the information you provide to us on through the Service to a third party or share your Personal Information to the company with which we enter into such transaction as a part of such transaction.

###  Security of Your Information

We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards designed to protect Personal Information, and our systems are designed to protect Personal Information from unauthorized usage on shared computers in that users are required to log in through our applications. Despite the actions and precautions we take, however, no data transmissions over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Consequently, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of your Personal Information and you transmit it to us at your own risk.

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose Personal Information through public facing aspects of the Service, that information can be collected and used by others. In short, by posting Personal Information online that is publicly accessible, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. We are not responsible for the security or privacy of any Personal Information you choose to submit in connection with any public features.

We may send an email to you at the email address you have provided to us in the event of a security breach. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing.

###  Third-Party Websites, Services and Applications

Please be aware that other websites and services, including the websites of third parties that you connect with through our Website or Service may collect personally identifiable information about you. This Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of those third-party websites, services or applications.

###  International Transfers

Personal Information collected through the Service may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which doesfollow or its affiliates, subsidiaries, agents or contractors maintain facilities, and by using the Service, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.

###  Contacting doesfollow

For questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at _info at doesfollow.com_.
